Hi, I'm Emily Larew and now I'm going to teach you how to do a wing and a toe.
So what's going to happen is this you're going to do a single wing.
So what we're going to do is we're going to start on our left foot and we're going to do, you're going to be on your right foot, all you're going to do is a single wing and add a toe drop in the back.
So, keep your toes forward; weight in the balls of your feet; use your plie.
Your going to push off your foot.
Toe.
You drop your toe in back right afterwards before you start your next wing.
Wing and a toe.
Good.
Let's try that left foot; we don't want to use and forget that one.
So ready?
We're going to use our right foot; plie your left foot and push off.
Wing and a toe.
So let's try it one more time, your right, my left.
We have, go lighter on the bar cause remember that's what our goal is we're working to go center floor not using the bar because you can't take this with you when you're doing a dance in front of everybody.
Ready?
So we have... good and that is how you do a wing and a toe.